Hello everyone, this is Teacher Tian,
This issue brings you specific guidance videos for the twelve treasure hiding places during the Treasure Hiding Month event.
And because the location given on this map is relatively vague, I will give the specific location here.
Then we go from number 1 to 12 and number 2 separately.
Then just pull down the progress bar below for the number you want. First is number one,
Number 1 is in the underground passage.
Then if you can see the specific location behind the two boxes in the middle,
It is the location of the previous crocodile nest. I won’t say much about how it got there. Then there's number two.
Number 2 is outside the cement factory, and then there is the iron tower on the right side of the bird's egg.
It can be seen on the stone pile next to the iron tower. No. 3,
No. 3 is on the shelf behind the compound point of the barracks pipeline and can be seen. Go there and have a look.
Next is No. 4. No. 4 is on the wooden box of the container below the visitor center.
Just look at the map for specific locations.
Sit here. Next is No. 5. The position of No. 5 is right next to the field supplies box on the river beach.
You can see it when you come under this red container. No. 6, this is behind the small military camp.
This is the trail, see the picture for the exact location. Then came number seven,
As for No. 7, it is on the road at the top of the dam, or behind the red container.
Then finally let’s talk about No. 8. No. 8 is the most important.
And this is the position of this treasure map that must be red, that is, the minimum is a pocket watch.
And the location is right here, coming from the container. Then this location is relatively secretive.
Then let me talk about this, there will be a three-second delay when it is turned on, be careful of the back sound.
And there are all good things in here.
Then go on to talk about No. 9, No. 9 is at the top of the dam, and then this container below the top of the dam,
Then this location is hidden quite secretly. Jump up here, in the corner of the red container, here,
You can see it here. Then let’s talk about No. 10. On No. 10, this position is also hidden deeper.
This one is on the right side of the road between the visitor center and the small military camp.
When you get here, there will be a pickup truck, on the left side of the pickup truck. There is a stone installation here,
Here in the corner of the stone installation. Then if you really don’t know the location, just look at the map.
Then we continue to talk about No. 11. No. 11 is at the small construction site on the left side of the administration.
It can be seen in this cement pipe near the wall. Finally, let’s talk about the 12th.
The location of No. 12 is in the cement factory.
In the middle of the cement plant, you can see it behind the sandbags at the angle between the cement truck and the middle.
Then all twelve points are like this. So see you in the next guide!
I hope everyone can find big red in their boxes!